YEN HUNG LIN

hello@yenhunglin.com yenhunglin.com

SKILLS

Computer Programs	Shop Skills
Sketch	Band saw
Invision	Bridgeport mill
-	Drill press
After Effects	Laser cutter
Cinema 4D	Miter saw
-	Painting
Photoshop	Sanding
Illustrator	Vacuum forming
InDesign	
-	
PTC Creo	Scripting Languages
Keyshot	HTML
	CSS
	JavaScript

Languages

Mandarin Chinese Taiwanese English

Other

Package model making ID Sketching

SELECTED RECOMMENDATIONS

Jonah Becker // VP, Industrial Design at Fitbit

Jeff spent a year as a graphic design contractor on my communications design team, and he supported a range of branding and packaging projects. Jeff is organized, professional, hard-working, and talented. He consistently delivered very high quality work and was a great person to have in the studio

Tim Kennedy // Communication Art Director at HTC

When Jeff joined our team at HTC San Francisco he started out in a blazing glory, and continued to shine for the duration of his time with us at HTC. Jeff's deft design skills and capable know how brought much needed support to our design team. While Jeff is a talented fellow, he's open-minded and has a willingness to explore new areas of design. Jeff has a genuine nature about him and is a kind, well-spoken man of may talents. I'd look forward to working with him again in the future!

SELECTED EXPERIENCES

Engagio // San Mateo, CA

2018-Present, UI, Visual Designer

Working with the marketing team, prduct team, and engineer team on defining the brand voice, generating marketing materials, and creating the best experience for the next generation account based marketing software.

MOCACARE // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan

2017-2018, UI/UX, Visual Designer

Working with the industrial design team and the product design team to locate user needs and to explore various solutions. Projects included MOCACARE hardware, packaging, and app.

HTC // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan

2014-2015, Visual, Package Designer

Working with the industrial and packaging team on packaging, animation, UI, and graphic design. Also accompanied designers to factories, met with vendors for study of new materials, and built a good work relationship with vendors.

San Francisco Art Institute // SF, CA

2014, Graphic Design Intern

In charge of weekly event poster designs, gallery show invitation designs, school publications, and school event photo documentation.

CCA Sputnik Design Studio // SF, CA

2013, Graphic Designer

In charge of Phase Forward: First Year Exhibition 2013, CCA 2013 Annual Fashion Show, Upstart: CCA Commencement Events 2013, CCA Fashion Design Promotion Fall 2013, and CCA President's Letter Fall 2013.

EDUCATION

California College of the Arts

2013, BFA in Graphic Design